Guide to the Rice University Art Gallery records, 1971-2017 UA 066
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Art Gallery records
1971-2017
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 066
26.25 Linear Feet (53 boxes)
2.51 Gigabytes Digital images of exhibit installations, opening and other events 1995-2011, accessible by request using identifier nearline UA0066aip_001.
In 1971 Sewall Hall was constructed making space available for a permanent art gallery at Rice University referred to as the Sewall Gallery and later as Rice University Art Gallery. These records reflect the exhibitions held there and related administrative functions.
Historical Sketch
In 1971, Sewall Hall was constructed making space available for a permanent art gallery at Rice University referred to as the Sewall Gallery. Originally the gallery was managed by faculty but soon had the benefit of a full time director. In 1994, it was renamed the Rice University Art Gallery.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of budget information, correspondence and many exhibition files that contain attendance, finances and general information on each exhibition. The files are arranged chronologically.
Restrictions on Access
This material is open for research. Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Provenance
Transfered June 25, 1998; July 24, 1998: March 8, 1999, 2008, 2015, 2016.
General
Includes the following digital objects stored in nearline system: UA0066aip_001
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges
Document Types
financial records
Places
Art
Subjects (Corporations)
Sewall Art Gallery; Rice University Art Gallery
- Series I: Office / Exhibition files, 1971-1989
  - Exhibition schedule, 1971-72 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Inaugural exhibition, 1971-72 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Architecture 100," 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Rice faculty exhibition, Dec. 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dorothy Hood, March 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Storyville photographs, Jan.-Feb. 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "Happenings" (Allen Kaprow) April 14, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6a)
  - "9th Annual Art Students Show," Apr. 28-May 20, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - "Prints and Drawings by Corbin Bennett," Mar. 30-Apr. 21, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lawrence Cassard donation, 1971-73 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Permanent collection on loan, 1972, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Exhibition schedule, 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Budget, 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - "Victoria's World," Sept. 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - "Six Rice Alumni," Nov.-Dec. 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Rice student traveling exhibition, Dec. 1972-Feb. 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - North American Indian photographs, Jan. 1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Juergen Strunck prints, Feb. 22-Mar. 9, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "10th Annual Art Students Exhibition," Apr. 16-May 12, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Exhibition schedule, 1973-74 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - "Options for Tomorrow's City," Aug.-Sept. 1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "Historian's Choice Exhibition," Oct. 18-Dec. 6, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - "Check Boterf Retrospective Exhibition," Dec. 14, 1973-Feb. 7, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - SMU/Rice graduate show, Feb. 18-Apr. 5, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - "11th Annual Art Students Show," Apr. 15-May 11, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Exhibitions (schedules, general), 1974-75 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Budget, 1974-75 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - "Prints by Stanley William Hayter," Aug. 27-Oct. 4, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Clement Meadmore sculpture, Oct. 16-Nov. 27, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Ryoji Akiyama photographs, Nov.-Dec. 1974 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - "An Exhibition of Paintings by Dodd-Groell-Gelber," Feb. 4-Mar. 21, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - "12th Annual Student Exhibition," Apr. 1-May 14, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Sewall Art Gallery departmental budgets, 1974-77 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Exhibitions (schedules, general), 1975-76 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Budget, 1975-76 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "Sculpture by Philip Ogle," Aug. 26-Oct. 3, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "Experiments in Visual/Verbal Communications" Work by Aaron Marcus," Oct. 15-Nov. 21, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - "Clay and Fiber," Dec. 4, 1975-Feb. 6,1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "American Painting, 1850/1975," Feb. 17-Mar. 31, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "13th Annual Art Students Exhibition," Mar. 14-May 8, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Misc. 1975-76 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Exhibitions (schedules, general), 1976-77 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Budget, 1976-77 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Garth Evans, 1976-77 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "Made of Paper," Aug.-Sept. 1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - "Drawings Today in New York," Oct. 13-Nov. 19, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - James Boynton-Roy Fridge, Dec. 1, 1976-Feb. 4, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - "Mexico: Before Columbus," Feb. 11-Mar. 31, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - "14th Annual Art Students Exhibition," Apr. 13-May 11, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Exhibitions (schedules, general), 1977-78 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Budget, 1977-78 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1977-79 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - "Seven New York Artists," Aug. 29-Oct. 7, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - "Cram, Goodhue and Ferguson: Plans and Architectural Drawings for the Development of the Rice Institute Campus, 1909-1930," Oct. 19-Nov. 19, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - "Rice Alumni Collections," Dec. 1, 1977-Feb. 3, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - "Photo-Realism," Dec. 1, 1977-Feb. 4, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Sculpture of Robert Murray, Feb. 14-Apr. 8, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - "Tsutsumu," 1977-78 [canceled] (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - "15th Annual Art Students' Exhibition," Apr. 18-May 14, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Exhibitions (schedules, general), 1978-79 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Budget, 1978-79 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Attendance, 1978-79 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - "American Illustration: 1800 to the Present," Sept. 1-Oct. 14, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Felix Eichenberg lecture, Oct. 4, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - "Pattern and Decoration," Nov. 2-Dec. 13, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Edward F. Heyne III donation, 1978-85 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Audit problems, 1978-86 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "The Architecture of Gunnar Asplund," Jan.10-Feb. 9, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - "Marden, Novros, Rothko: Coda to an Exhibition," Mar. 5-Apr. 4, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - "16th Annual Art Students' Exhibition," Apr. 11-May 12, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Budget, 1979-80 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Budget, 1979-80 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Attendance, 1979-80 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - "Costumes from the Arab World," Sept. 5-Oct. 18, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - "Costumes from the Arab World," CACH final report, financial (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - "Civic Art in Houston Since 1900," Nov. 3-Dec. 5, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - "Civic Art in Houston Since 1900," loans (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - "Recent Color Photography," Jan.16-Feb. 13, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - "Selections/Rice University Art Collection," Mar. 7-Apr. 2, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - "Student Show 79/80," Apr. 16-May 10, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Bukowksi donation, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Exhibitions (schedule, general), 1980-81 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Budget, 1980-81 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Sewall report, 1980-81 (Box 5)
  - "Art from Houston Corporations I," Sept. 10-Oct.11, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - "Art from Houston Corporations I" (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - "Art from Houston Corporations I" (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - "Felix Bracquemond and the Etching Process," Oct. 22-Nov. 11, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - "Emerging Texas Photographers," Nov. 18-Dec. 10, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - "Emerging Texas Photographers," CACH grant (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - "Time After Time: Reflections of the Classical Past," Jan. 13-Feb. 28, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - "Allen Jones, Works on Paper-A Retrospective," Mar. 10-Apr. 11, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - "Allen Jones…" (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - "Allen Jones…" (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - "Allen Jones…," CACH grant (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - "18th Annual Students' Exhibition," Apr. 21-May 12, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Attendance, 1980-90 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Attendance, 1980-92 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Exhibitions (schedules, general), 1981-82 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Budget, 1981-82 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Press releases, 1981-82 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Sewall report, 1981-82 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Special events, 1981-82 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1981-82 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - "CIBA-GEIGY Collects: Aspects of Abstraction," Sept. 8-Oct. 24, 1981; publicity (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - "CIBA-GEIGY…," loans (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - "CIBA-GEIGY…," corresp. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - "CIBA-GEIGY…," lecture (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - "CIBA-GEIGY…," special events (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - "Variants: Drawings by Contemporary Sculptors," Nov. 2-Dec. 12, 1981; publicity (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - "Variants…," contracts (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - "Variants…," loans (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - "Variants…," expenses (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - "Variants…," CACH grant (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - "Variants…," travel (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - "Variants…," condition reports (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - "Leonardo's Return to Vinci: The Countess de Béhague Collection," 1981-82 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - "Leonardo's…," contracts (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - "Leonardo's…," installation (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - "Leonardo's…," budget (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - "Leonardo's…," expenses (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - "Leonardo's…," photos (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - "Leonardo's…," publicity (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - "Leonardo's…," corresp. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - "Leonardo's…," special events (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - "L'Esprit Moderne," Mar. 9-Apr. 8, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - "L'Esprit Moderne," walking guide (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - "L'Esprit Moderne," publicity (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - "19th Annual Students' Exhibition," Apr. 19-May 8, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - "Islamic Rugs," May 20-June 7, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Exhibits (schedules, general), 1982-83 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Budget, 1982-83 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Sewall report, 1982-83 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1982-83 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - "David Hockney: Sources and Experiments," Sept. 7-Oct. 15, 1982; publicity (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "David Hockney…," notes (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - "David Hockney…," Picasso loans (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - "David Hockney…," loans (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - "David Hockney…," photos (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "On the Leading Edge: Tony Robbin," Oct. 26-Nov. 20, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - "…Tony Robbin," installation (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - "…Tony Robbin," publicity (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - "…Tony Robbin," corresp. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - "…Tony Robbin," related events (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - "Earl Staley's recent Mediterranean Sketches," Dec. 3, 1982-Jan. 8, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - "Art of Metal in Africa," Feb. 4-Apr. 9, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - "Art of Metal in Africa," publicity (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - "Art of Metal in Africa," related events (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - "20th Annual Student Exhibition," Apr. 18-May 7, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Educational Component, 1982-83; corresp. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Educational Component, 1982-83; packet (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Educational Component, 1982-83; school groups (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Educational Component, 1982-83; publicity (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Educational Component, 1982-83; slides (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Financial, 1983-84 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1983-84 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Sewall Art Gallery Committee notes, 1983-84 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - "George Smith New Works," Sept. 16-Oct. 29, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - "Function Follows Art," Nov. 11-Dec. 10, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - "Out of the Forties, a Portrait of Texas," Jan. 27-Mar. 17, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - "Artists and the War: French Patriotic Posters, 1914-1920," Mar. 29-Apr. 21, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - "21st Annual Rice Students Art Show," May 2-12, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1983-85 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - General gallery publicity, 1984-85 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1984-85 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - "Festival Indonesia: Primitive Textiles and Contemporary Paintings," Sept. 14-Oct. 20, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - "Festival Indonesia…," loans (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - "Basilois Poulos, Recent Painting and Works on Paper," Nov. 2-Dec. 15, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - "Monumental Islamic Calligraphy from India," Jan. 25-Mar. 11, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - "Red Grooms/Warrington Colescott: Masters of Contemporary Satire," Mar. 15-Apr. 13, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - "22nd Annual Rice Art Students Exhibition," Apr. 23-May 11, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Gifts, pending, 1984-88 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1985-86 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Sewall report, 1985-86 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - "Fabled Cloth: Batik from Java's North Coast," Sept. 5-Oct. 19, 1985; corresp. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - "Fabled Cloth…," installation (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - "Fabled Cloth…," visuals (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - "Fabled Cloth…," publicity (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - "1985 Alumni Art Exhibition III," Nov. 1-2, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - "Souvenirs: Work by Barbara Hanger, Kit Hillery and Suzanne Mitchell," Nov. 8-Dec. 14, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - "Dig We Must! Archaeology at Rice," Jan. 31-Feb. 29, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - "Hispania Nostra," Mar. 13-Apr. 12, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - "Visions of a Third Eye: Photographs from the Rice University Art Collection," Mar. 14-Apr. 12, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - "23rd Annual Rice Art Students Show," Apr. 22-May 10, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Loan audit, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1986-87 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Sewall report, 1986-87 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - "A Place of Dreams: Houston, An American City," Sept 5-Oct. 18, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - "Rice Art Faculty," Oct. 31-Dec. 6, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - "Expressionism, Sight and Sound," Jan. 30-Mar. 27, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - "Expressionism…," loans (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - "Tea Wares of Contemporary Japan," Jan. 30-Mar. 27, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - "Tea Wares…," loans (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - "24th Rice Art Students Exhibition," Apr. 21-May 9, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Jerome Segal bequest, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1987-88 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Fire and security systems, 1987-88 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Sewall report, 1987-88 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - "Jan Schoonhoven: A Retrospective," Sept. 4-Oct. 16, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - "Jan Schoonhoven…," publicity (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - "Jan Schoonhoven…," loans (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - "Jan Schoonhoven…," loans (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - "Cavalieri e Draghi," Oct. 17-Nov. 25, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - "Modern Masters," Jan. 16-Feb. 20, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - "Portrayals," Mar. 4-Apr. 6, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - "Silver Anniversary Art Students Exhibition," Apr. 19-May 7, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Greensheets, July 1, 1986-June 30,1987; July 1, 1987-June 30, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Cohen House collection loan, 1987-90 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1988-89 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Financial, 1988-89 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Collection overview, 1988-89 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - "Rice Faculty Show: An Art Celebration," Sept. 16-Oct. 26, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - "Drawn from Life: Contemporary Interpretative Landscape," Nov. 10- Dec. 16, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - "Drawn from Life…" (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - "Drawn from Life…," loans (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - "Drawn from Life…," visuals (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - "Large Scale/Small Scale," Jan. 19-Feb. 28, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Series II: Office / Exhibition files, 1989-2005
  - "Visions of the 20th Century on the French Revolution: The George Soria Collection," Mar. 21-Apr. 21, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - "Visions…," visuals (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - "26th Annual Rice Art Students Exhibition," Apr. 25-May 13, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Loan audit, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Loan audit, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Visiting Committee (consultants), 1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Consultants report, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - General gallery corresp., 1989-90 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - General gallery budgets, 1989-90 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Cost data and gallery reports, 1989-90 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - MAP I application, 1989-90 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Collection overview, 1989-90 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - "Harriet Shorr: Paintings and Pastels," Aug. 21- Oct. 28, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - "Harriet Shorr…," visuals (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - "Messages from the South," Nov. 7-Dec. 20, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - "Messages from the South" (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - "Messages from the South," corresp. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - "Messages from the South," résumés (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - "Dutch Geometric Abstraction in the '80s," Jan. 11-Feb. 10, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - "Other Images/Other Realities: Mexican Photography Since 1930," Feb. 16-Apr. 8, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - "Other Images…" (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - "Other Images…," travel (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - "Other Images…," slides (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - "Other Images…," catalog sales (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Theodore F. Wolff lecture, Apr. 5, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - "27th Annual Rice Student Art Exhibition," Apr. 19-May 5, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Attendants, 1989-90 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Collection position statement, 1989, 92 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Space planning, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Woodson Research Center objects, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Vernon Fisher repairs, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Budget, 1990-91 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Budget, 1990-91 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Check requests, 1990-91 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Check requests, 1990-91 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Gallery general accounts, 1990-91 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Purchase orders, 1990-91 (Box 17)
  - Interdepartmental transfers, 1990-91 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Collection overview, 1990-91 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Attendants, 1990-91 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Newsletter, 1990-91 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - "Not Just Another Faculty Show: Rice Faculty Select Works from the Menil Collection and the Museum of Fine Arts, Houston," Aug. 21-Sept. 29, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - "Not Just Another…" (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - "Rice Highlights from the 1990 Economic Summit of Industrialized Nations," Sept. 21-Nov. 11, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - "Modern Indonesian Art: Three Generations of Tradition and Change," Oct. 13-Dec. 20, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - "Modern Indonesian Art…," condition reports (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Rauschenberg book, Nov. 1990 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - "California Monoprints," Jan. 11-Feb. 16, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - "California Monoprints," condition reports (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - "Selections from the Rice Collection: A Tribute to Donors," Mar. 7-Apr. 10, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - "Selections from…" (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - "28th Annual Student Exhibition," Apr. 18-May 4, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Publicity, 1990-93 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Friends of Sewall Art Gallery budget, 1990-93 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Collection management policy, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Photography audit, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Budget, 1991-92 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Budget, 1991-92 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Purchase orders, 1991-92 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Gallery general accounts, 1991-92 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - General gallery expenses, 1991-92 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Interdepartmental transfers, 1991-92 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Check requests, 1991-92 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Financial corresp., 1991-92 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - General gallery corresp., 1991-92 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Student timesheets, 1991-92 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - MAP I, 1991-92 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Catalog sales, 1991-92 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - "Creative Partners," Aug. 20-Oct. 12, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - "Gorilla Girls," Jan. 15-Feb. 8, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - "India Along the Ganges," Feb. 20-Mar. 28, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - "India Along the Ganges," condition reports (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - "29th Annual Student Exhibition," Apr. 16-May 2, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Information technology, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Collection-missing pieces, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Student statements on collection, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Budget, 1992-93 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Accounting record, 1992-93 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Check requests, 1992-93 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Purchase orders, 1992-93 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - General gallery expenditures, 1992-93 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Interdepartmental transfers, 1992-93 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Student timesheets, 1992-93 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - MAP II report, 1992-93 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - "Karin Broker: Searching for a Saint," Sept. 3-Oct. 10, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - "Karin Broker…," condition reports (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - "Twentieth-Century Texas Folk Art," Oct. 22-Dec. 12, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - "…Texas Folk Art," condition reports (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - "Small-Scale Sculpture," Oct. 24-Dec. 14, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - "Recent Gifts to the Rice University Art Collection," Jan. 14-Feb. 13, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - "Recent Gifts…" reception, Jan. 1993 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - "Contemporary Realist Watercolor," Feb. 25-Apr. 10, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - "30th Rice Student Exhibition," Apr. 22-May 8, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Financial, 1992-94 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Edward F. Heyne, III donation, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Signage, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Exhibitions (schedules, general), 1993-94 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Budget, 1993-94 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Budget history to 1993-94 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - "John Sparagana: 1990-1993," Sept. 2-Oct. 9, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - "The Mask in Contemporary Art/The African Mask," Oct. 21-Dec. 11, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - "Enlightening the Classics: 18th Century Etchings of Ancient Roman Architecture," Jan. 13-Feb. 19, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - "Four Master Photographers: Bravo, Doisneau, Erwitt, and Kertész," Mar. 10-Apr. 14, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - "31st Rice Student Exhibition," Apr. 21-May 7, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Demographic Survey and Information of Rice Art/Art History Alumni, April 21, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Exhibitions, 1994-95 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - "Short Stories: In One Minute of Less," Nov. 4-23, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - "Michael Shaughnessy New Installation," Jan. 26-Mar. 2, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - "Rice University Student Art Exhibition No. 33," Apr. 26-May 11, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Exhibitions 1996-97 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - "Beyond the Bushes," Sept. 22-Nov. 3, 1996 [canceled] (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - "The Urge to be Transported," Sept. 27-Nov. 3, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - "Facts are Slippery," Nov. 15-Dec. 15, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Exhibitions 1997-98 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - "Doña Provi's Garden," Jan. 8-Feb. 15, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Photos of necklet presented to Rice University, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Misc. - not dated, VHS tape: "Sculpture: 30 Days Work, Anthony Cafritz and Lincoln Schatz," VHS tape: "Texas Folk Art," VHS tape: "AIDS Awareness Project: Day Without Art," Dec. 1, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - "Stephen Keene: Fresh Art Daily," 1998-99 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - "Behavior," 1998-99 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - "Michael Petry: The History of the World," 1998-99 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - "Jane Miller: Time Not Wasted," 1999 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - 36th Student Show, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - "Hoss," 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - "Shout Outs," 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - "Superthrive," 2000 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - "Clubs of Bamako," 2000 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - "Check it Out," April 2000 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - "Kastenhaus," 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - "Manly on the Plaid," November-December, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Video Cassettes (Box 22, Folder 29)